{
    "subject": "Donald_Knuth",
    "predicate": "isKnownFor",
    "object": "TeX",
    "human_readable": "Donald Knuth is known for TeX.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8782055377960205,
            "question": "What is Donald Knuth known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4675414562225342,
            "question": "Can you name a system Donald Knuth developed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4003297984600067,
            "question": "What field of study is Donald Knuth associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30312877893447876,
            "question": "What other notable contributions has Donald Knuth made to computer science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29142704606056213,
            "question": "TeX is primarily used for what purpose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19486424326896667,
            "question": "Who created the TeX typesetting system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17973272502422333,
            "question": "Is TeX still widely used today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15116554498672485,
            "question": "What are some examples of documents that use TeX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10471376776695251,
            "question": "What makes TeX a unique typesetting system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08953604102134705,
            "question": "How has TeX impacted the field of publishing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Donald Knuth is known for TeX.",
            "html": "yago_31587_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes TeX a unique typesetting system?",
            "html": "yago_31587_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of documents that use TeX?",
            "html": "yago_31587_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is TeX still widely used today?",
            "html": "yago_31587_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31587_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* Donald Knuth is indeed associated with TeX, as mentioned in multiple documents (e.g., \"Donald Knuth revolutionized computer science by introducing rigorous analysis and mathematical principles to the design and analysis of algorithms.\", which also mentions TeX; and \"Donald Knuth created the TeX typesetting system\", among others).\n* Donald Knuth is also associated with \"The Art of Computer Programming\" in multiple documents.\n* There are no contradictions or conflicting information regarding these associations.\n\nTherefore, based on this evaluation, I would say that:\n\n`{ 'output': 'yes' }`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support the statement that Donald Knuth is known for TeX, as multiple sources mention his creation and contribution to this typesetting system."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}